A paid vacation?!
有給休暇？
Yeah, I thought I better go see my daughter
ええ　そろそろ娘に会っとかないと
before she forgets what her father looks like.
いい加減 顔忘れられそうで
It's not like you to want to go visit your hometown.
里帰りなんて 君らしくないな
Not to mention you ignored our calls the other day.
こないだも出動要請すっぽかしたりさ
It was just a thought. If it's not possible, then that's fine.
あっ いや ちょっと思っただけで
いや別に無理だったらいいんスよ
After all, the safety of the city comes first!
何より市民の安全が最優先なんで
I didn't say it's not possible, but...
いや
無理ってわけじゃないんだけどね
Sounds okay with me.
いいんじゃないですか？
I can handle things by myself for a while.
少しくらいなら
僕１人でも大丈夫ですよ
Well, if you say so, Barnaby.
バーナビー君がそう言うなら　まあ…
Go and spend some quality time with your daughter.
たまにはゆっくり
娘さんに会ってあげてください
She's one of my important fans, after all.
彼女は大切な
僕のファンでもあるんですから
にひひ あは…
What am I supposed to say when I give this to her?
何て言って渡しゃいいんだ？
これ…
You should start thinking about what to do with your life.
お前も今後の身の振り方を
考えたほうがいいんじゃないか？
yabureta PAGE wa ubawaretanda yo
That torn page was stolen,
破れたページは
奪われたんだよ
dokoka de otoshita oboe wa nai kara
since I don't remember ever dropping it anywhere.
何処かで落とした
覚えはないから
iwakan mo nai hodo kirei ni nai soko ni wa
In the place where the page used to be,
違和感もないほど
綺麗にないそこには
yume to iu nano shou ga tashikani atta
there was a chapter entitled "Dreams."
夢という名の章が確かにあった
nani wo nikumeba ii? kako ka jibun jishin ka
But who should I blame? The past? Myself?
何を憎めばいい？
過去か自分自身か
dekireba hoka no dareka de are
If possible, I hope it's someone else.
出来れば他の誰かであれ
monogatari no bokura ga sono mirai wo omou no wa
We, the characters in the story, think of the future.
物語の僕らが
その未来想うのは
nakushita ato demo shuyaku wa kawarenai kara
Because even after we're gone, the main character can't change.
失くした後でも
主役は変われないから
shousan nante sarenakutatte tashikana kyou ga aru nara
Even if I'm not praised, as long as today is here,
賞賛なんてされなくたって
確かな今日があるなら
yume nante namae no shou wa ikura demo tsukurerunda
I can make as many chapters as I want entitled "Dreams."
夢なんて名前の章は
いくらでも創れるんだ
ふう
ん？
Do you need some help, sir?
何かお困りのようで？
いや ヒーローさんの出る幕じゃない
I don't need a Hero to handle this.
It's nothing I can't do on my own.
ちょっとラジエーターの
調子が悪いだけだ
How long are you going to keep driving that clunker, Bro?
そんなポンコツ
いつまで乗ってんだよ　兄貴？
It's not a clunker.
ポンコツじゃない
It's vintage, Kotetsu.
これはヴィンテージだ　虎徹
That depends on how you look at it.
ものは言いようだな
You don't see anyone driving second-hand junk like that
今どきシュテルンビルトじゃ
走ってねえぞ？
こんな中古のボロ
in Stern Bild anymore.
ここじゃしっかり走ってるんだよ
It runs just fine here.
Just get in already.
いいから早く乗れ
I'm surprised you came to pick me up.
わざわざ迎えに来てくれるなんて
らしくねえな
Getting soft in your old age?
歳か？
I only came because Mom asked me to.
母さんに頼まれただけだ
ん？
What, you're not going to come in?
なんだ　寄ってかねえのか？
I'm in the middle of deliveries.
配達の途中だからな
こう見えて 忙しいんだ　俺は
You may not think so, but I'm quite busy.
Your little brother came home for the first time in years.
久しぶりに弟が帰ってきてんだ
At least stay for a cup of tea.
お茶の一杯でも飲んでけよ
If you want to talk, come by my store.
話があるなら店に来い
I'll keep the place opened tonight for old times' sake.
兄弟のよしみだ
夜でも開けてやる
He's always so straight-laced...
相変わらず堅物だな
This place is the same as always too.
こっちも相変わらずだ
I'm home!
ただいま〜
Huh?
あり？
ん？
Mom!
母ちゃん
I'm back.
帰ったよ
あら虎徹
Oh, Kotetsu. You're here early.
意外と早かったのね
まあな
Yeah. You seem to be doing well.
思ったより元気そうだな
Thankfully. How about you?
おかげさまでね
あんたは？
Huh?
え？
I'm doing just fine.
いや　俺もまあ…
ぼちぼちってところだ
ホントに？
何かあったんじゃないの？
You sure? Did something happen?
別に…
Nope.
何もねえって
Not a thing.
そう　ならいいけどね
Okay. Well, if you say so.
I was just surprised when you said that you were coming home.
突然帰るだなんて言うから
びっくりしたわよ
Say, is Kaede still at school?
なあ？　楓ってまだ学校？
そうね　もう帰ってくると思うけど？
Yeah. She should be coming home soon, though.
I see.
あそっか…
I knew it.
やっぱり ちょっと元気がないわね
You don't look all too well.
No... It's not like that, Mom.
いや あの あのな母ちゃん
You're all wilted.
元気ないわ
Oh, you were talking to the plant...
あ そっちね
久しぶりだな〜
この部屋も机も
It's been a while since I've seen this room and this desk.
え？ ええええ！
What the—?!
What is this?! She's been collecting these?
んっだ
こんなのとってやがんのか　あいつ
おっ
あっ
はあ
お父さん？
Dad?!
くっ
楓！
Kaede!
驚いたか？
久しぶりだな〜
Surprised to see me? It's been a while.
パパ帰ってきたぞ〜
Daddy's home!
Why are you in my room?!
何で私の部屋に入ってんの？
え？
Huh?
勝手に入らないで
Don't go in without my permission.
But why not? I mean, this used to be Daddy's room.
いいだろ〜？
だってここは元々は
パパの部屋なんだし
You went through my stuff?
引き出し開けたの？
Oh, well, umm...
ああ…　いや…　それは…
Boy, you sure have gotten big, Kaede.
しっかし大きくなったな〜　楓
How many stories tall are you now?
今 身長何百メートルだ？
ん？
ぬっ
よ〜しっ
I know!
How about we go take a bath together tonight!
今日はパパと久しぶりに
お風呂にでも入る…
Pervert!
変態！
変態？
Pervert? Where did you learn a word like that?
おま…
そんな言葉どこで覚えたんだ？
変態
Pervert! Pervert! Pervert!
変態！　変態！
出てって！
Get out!
や…　あ う…
H-Hey, Kaede?
おい 楓！
ふんっ
ほら虎徹
もっと野菜食べなさい　野菜
Come on, Kotetsu. Eat more vegetables.
どうせバカの一つ覚えの
チャーハンしか食べてないんでしょ？
You probably only eat fried rice,
since it's the only thing you know how to make, right?
あんた
What's wrong with fried rice? Fried rice is good too, you know.
別にいいじゃねえか チャーハン
どこが悪いんだよ チャーハン
Thank you for the food.
ごちそうさま
Hey, Kaede... Are you still mad?
あ おい 楓
まだ怒ってんのか？
怒ってんのか じゃないでしょ？
Listen to yourself. Have you apologized to Kaede?
あんた ちゃんと楓に謝ったの？
Well, no...
あ いや…
勝手に娘の引き出しなんか開けて
Going through your daughter's stuff like that.
あの子も もう10歳なのよ？
She's already ten years old, you know?
ん…
I'm so sorry, Kaede.
ごめん 楓
パパ勝手に部屋に入って
悪かったってば
Daddy shouldn't have gone into your room like that.
なあって
Come on, forgive me. Pretty please, Kaede?
いい加減パパを許してくれってば
楓〜　頼むよ〜
その話し方やめて！
Stop talking to me like that!
あ！　そうだ！
Oh, yeah! Daddy got an autograph from Barnaby!
パパ バーナビーのサイン
もらってきたんだ
もし楓がパパを許してくれ…
If you forgive me...
それホント？
Really?!
すっご〜い
どうやってもらったの？
I don't believe it! How did you get it?!
あ いや…
Well...
お前のために徹夜で
写真集の発売日に並んでさ
I stood in line all night at a photo book release just for you.
わあ やった〜！　ありがとう！
Yay! Thank you!
あ じゃそうだ！　楓
So, Kaede! Do you want to sleep in Daddy's room tonight?
今日はパパと一緒に寝るか？
That's a completely different issue!
それとこれとは別！
え…　え…
Can't believe that kid's already ten years old...
あのチビがもう10歳か
ちょっと会わないうちに
どんどん変わってくな
She's changed so much since I last saw her.
What happened, Kotetsu?
何があったんだ？　虎徹
ん？
いや 別に何も
Nothing happened.
You came here to talk, didn't you?
話があるから店へ来たんだろ？
Oh, it's nothing important. I'm all right.
ああ
特に話っていうほどのことでもねえよ
だいじょぶだ
お前 何で帰ってきたんだ？
Why did you come back home?
Why? Well...
なんでって
いやそりゃ…
Mom is worried about you too.
母さんも心配してたぞ
ああ…
Fine...
まあいい
ただ いい歳して
親に心配かけるような真似は
But a guy your age isn't supposed to make his mother
あまり感心しないがな
worry like that.
What's your problem?
何だよ
Are you saying I need a reason to come home?
理由がないと
帰ってきちゃいけねえってのか？
別にそうは言ってない
I didn't say that.
そう聞こえたから言ってんだ
That's what it sounded like to me.
忙しいとこ邪魔したのは悪かったよ
Hey, I'm sorry I barged in on you. But this is my hometown.
けどここは俺の田舎だろ
Why are you so irritated?
何をピリピリしてるんだ？
I'm not irritated! I'm telling you to leave me alone!
ピリピリなんかしてねえよ！
ほっといてくれって言ってんだ
なら帰って来なければいい
Then why bother coming back?
俺には俺の事情があるんだよ
I've got my own things to deal with!
Why can't you understand?!
わかってくれよ
I can't understand unless you tell me what's bothering you!
言ってくれなきゃ俺だってわからん！
ん…
そう肩肘張るな虎徹
Don't try to act so tough, Kotetsu.
いいか？　ここでのお前は
ワイルドタイガーじゃない
Listen... Over here, you're not Wild Tiger.
鏑木虎徹
You're Kotetsu Kaburagi, my little brother.
俺の弟なんだ
能力減退？
Your powers are declining?
Yeah.
ああ　使う度に
時間がどんどん短くなっていく
The time in which I can use them gets shorter and shorter.
If I lose my powers, I may not be able to continue being a Hero.
このまま能力がなくなったら
俺はヒーローを
続けられねえかもしれねえ
When I think about that, I don't know what to do.
そう考えると
どうしていいか わからなくて
I see.
そういうことか
I know there's nothing I can do about it.
自分でも どうしようもねえって事ぐらい
わかってんだ
けど…　けどよ…
I know that, but!
I've made a lot of sacrifices to get to where I am today.
俺は色んなものを犠牲にしながら
ここまでずっとやってきたんだ
なのに こんなことで
終わっちまうのかって思うと
And this is how it's all going to end?
Why didn't you tell me about this right away?
どうしてすぐ話さなかったんだ
How could I?
言えるかよ　こんなこと
昔からお前はそうやって
You always did try to keep everything to yourself.
すぐ１人で
抱え込もうとするところがある
悪いくせだぞ
It's a bad habit of yours.
お前が能力に目覚めたときと
You did the same thing when you first discovered your powers.
まるで同じだ
くっ
Worrying about it won't give you any answers.
悩んだところで
答えの出る話じゃない
今はゆっくり休め
Try to rest for now. That's why you came back, right?
そのために帰ってきたんだろ？
I know.
わかってるよ
Kotetsu...
虎徹
Two dollars.
２ドルだ
ああ？
What?!
ちっ
ふんっ
Kotetsu...
虎徹
ちっ
What is it?
何だよ？
例え能力がなくなったとしても
Even if you lose your powers, your life isn't over.
別にお前のすべてが
終わるわけじゃないぞ
He's done it again!
絶好調！　バーナビー人命救助！
Barnaby has saved people from a fire!
今シーズンも快調に首位を独走中！
He continues to stay on top of the chart for this season!
僕１人でも大丈夫ですから
I can handle things by myself.
ランキングはただの結果です
My ranking is just incidental. Protecting people at all times...
いつでも市民を守る
それがヒーローの使命ですから
That's what we Heroes do.
A Hero must protect people at all times, right?
どんなときでも市民を守るのが
ヒーローでしょ？
I know that, but...
それはわかってるけど
Then what are you waiting for?
じゃ何をぼやぼやしてるの？
だって 今はお前が！
But right now, you're...
ちっ
Fine, I'll go. Are you happy now?
ああ わかったよ
行きゃいいんだろ？　行きゃ
Yes, I am.
それでいいの
あなたはどんなときでも
ヒーローでいて
No matter what happens, please be a Hero.
約束よ
Promise me that.
And there's Wild Tiger!
ここでワイルドタイガーだ！
さすが壊し屋
ビルを壊して人命救助！
The Crusher for Justice has just saved lives
by destroying the building!
What?!
ええ？
Tomoe?!
友恵！
あの後 容態が急変して…
Her condition suddenly worsened right after you left...
Guess this is it for me...
もう 潮時なのかもな
I'm sorry, Tomoe...
ごめんな 友恵
このままじゃ お前との約束
I don't think I can keep my promise.
守っていけそうにねえや
Dad!
お父さん！
ねえ お父さん起きてよ！
Dad, wake up!
ねえ！　おばあちゃんが！
It's Grandma, she's...!
お父さん！
Dad!
ん？
何だよ　ばあちゃんがどうしたって？
What? What about Grandma?
Mom! What's wrong?!
母ちゃん！　どうした！
どあっ　おい 母ちゃん！
Hey, Mom!
動かさないで！
Don't shake me!
え？
腰を痛めただけだから
I just hurt my back!
Huh?
へ？
急に寒くなったからかしらね
I wonder if it's because it suddenly got colder.
あたたた…
Ow ow ow...
おい虎徹！
Hey, Kotetsu!
母さん倒れたんだって？
I heard that Mom collapsed!
Huh?
え？
ったく
そんな大騒ぎすることじゃないだろ
Jeez. It's not something to make such a big fuss about.
まあ 私が急に倒れたのは事実だから
仕方がないわよ
Don't be so hard on her. It's true that I collapsed.
Sorry about that, Kaede.
ごめんね　楓
んん…
ほれ　おばあちゃんは
たいしたことなかったんだ
Come on. Grandma's just fine. Hurry up and go to school.
早く学校行きなさい
But...
でも…
No "buts." Do as I say!
でもじゃないだろ
パパの言うことを聞きなさい
ん…
I told you that Grandma's fine. Why don't you understand?
だから おばあちゃんなら
大丈夫だって言ってんだろ？
わからねえやつだな
Besides, I'm here today.
それに今日はパパだっている…
わかってないのはお父さんでしょ？
You're the one who doesn't understand!
え？
大っ嫌い！　お父さんなんか！
I hate you, Dad!
楓…
Kaede...
KABURAGI
FAMILY
GRAVE
はあ…
俺はいったいどうしたらいいんだ
What should I do, Tomoe?
友恵
何だかわかんねえけど
楓にも嫌われたみたいだし
I don't know why, but Kaede hates me.
もう６年になるのか
It's been six years already, huh?
ん？
I was making deliveries in the area, so I stopped by.
配達で近くに来たんでな
Sorry for all the fuss Kaede made this morning.
今日は朝から何だか楓が
騒がせて悪かったな
昨日といい今日といい
ほんっと世話が焼ける親子だよ
First you, and now Kaede... You two sure are a handful.
お前たちは
んん…
Do you know why Kaede got so upset this morning?
なあ　今朝 楓がどうしてあんなに
取り乱したかわかるか？
え？
あの子にはな
もう母さんしかいないんだ
Our mom is all that she has left.
お前がそばにいてやれない今
Since you can't be by her side, she's afraid
もしも母さんに何かあったら
she's going to be left alone if she loses her grandmother.
自分は一人ぼっちに
なるんじゃないかって
そういう不安を抱えて
暮らしてるんだよ
She lives with that fear every day.
That's why she gets upset even at the slightest things.
だからちょっとしたことに
過敏にもなる
I hate to bring this up,
言いたかないが 友恵さんが
亡くなったときのことだってあるしな
but she already went through the loss of her mother.
So that's why...
そういうことか
I'm not trying to blame you for what happened.
別に今さら お前を責めるつもりはない
You have your own life to live.
お前にはお前の生き方がある
ただ 楓はいつも心細い思いをしている
But Kaede is always feeling lonely.
Try to understand that.
そこはわかってやれ
はあ はあ はあ…
わかってないのはお父さんでしょ！
You're the one who doesn't understand!
Guess I really didn't understand a thing about Kaede...
結局 俺は楓のことを
何にもわかってなかったってことか
あ？
母ちゃん！
Mom?!
What are you doing?! You should be lying down!
何やってんだよ！
寝てなきゃダメだろ
もう大丈夫　このとおりよ
I'm all right now. See?
Who cares about some cabbages? Think about your age.
キャベツなんて
どうでもいいじゃねえか
歳を考えろよ
そんなことしてっから
腰痛めちまうんだぞ？
That's what caused you to hurt your back in the first place!
せっかく手塩にかけて育てたのに
I put so much effort into raising these kids.
元気がないのをほっとくわけにも
いかないでしょ？
I can't just ignore them when they're not doing so well.
And that goes the same for you too.
あんたもキャベツも
I'm not a vegetable, Mom.
野菜と一緒にすんな
どうか どうかおばあちゃんを
助けてあげてください
Please... Please help Grandma! God, I beg you!
神様 お願いします
もしおばあちゃんがいなくなったら
If I lose Grandma, I don't know what I'll do...
あたし…
母ちゃん
楓のやつ 傘持ってんのかな？
Mom, you think Kaede took an umbrella with her?
きゃあ！
ひ…
いやっ
きゃああ！
あああ
くっ うう…
ううん…
くっ…
ああ！
誰か！
Someone help!
Is anyone there?!
誰かいませんか？
はい はい　ああ いいえ
どうもすみません
Yes. Yes. No. Thank you very much.
What did they say, Mom?
ええ 何だって？　母ちゃん
It seems she left school.
学校からはちゃんと帰ったそうよ
友達のところにも行ってないみたい
And she hasn't gone to any of her friends' houses either.
そっか…
I see.
Still can't get through to her cellphone.
相変わらず携帯は繋がらねえし
I'm going to look around the area.
ちょっと その辺見てくる
Kaede!
楓！　どこだ！
Where are you?! Kaede!
楓！
Did you find her, Kotetsu?
見つかったか？　虎徹
No. What about you?
いや　そっちは？
Look at this rain.
この雨だ　楓どころか
人っ子一人いやしないよ
There isn't anyone around, let alone Kaede.
どこかその辺で
雨宿りしているだけならいいんだが
I hope she's just taking shelter from the rain somewhere.
ああ…
きゃ！
Kaede! It's Daddy!
楓！　パパだぞ！
Kaede!
返事しろ 楓！
Answer me! Kaede!
あっ
ちっ
I'll have to take my chances.
こうなったら一か八かだ
おい　力を使って闇雲に
探し回ったところで
Hey, using your powers and searching around aimlessly
won't do you any good.
らちが明かないぞ
I know that.
わかってる
少しだけ静かにしててくれ
Just be quiet for a bit.
I'm almost out of time!
もう時間がねえ　楓 頼む！
Kaede... Please...
Say something.
何かしゃべってくれ！
Dad...
お父さん　助けて
Help...
お父さん
Dad!
くうっ！
う…　う…
Kaede!
楓！
あっ
Are you in there, Kaede?!
そこにいるんだろ？　楓！
お父さん！
Dad!
Yeah, it's Daddy!
おう　パパだ！
You must have been terrified.
怖かっただろ？
今すぐここから出してやるからな！
I'll get you out right away!
Everything's going to be fine.
もう安心だ
くっ
のあああ くっ！
ぐおああああ！
What? Not now!
なっ！　ここでかよ！
Dad?!
お父さん！
あっ
心配するな楓！
It's okay, Kaede.
あっ
Your daddy is Kaburagi Kotetsu. He won't give up so easily!
お前のパパはな！
鏑木虎徹は
そう簡単には終わらねえからよ！
ああ！
でい くっ　おあ！
What good is a Hero... if he can't even save his own daughter!
娘一人助けられねえで
何がヒーローだ！
楓！
Kaede!
はあっ はっ
Dad!
お父さん！
楓！
Kaede!
You're safe now.
もうだいじょぶだ
I'm sorry, Dad. I'm so sorry.
ごめんなさい　お父さん
ごめんなさい
私…
It's all right, Kaede. Daddy is sorry too.
いいんだ 楓
パパこそ悪かった
I'm sorry for making you feel so lonely.
ずっと一人にしてごめんな
はっ はっ はっ
あは
Heading back already? You barely had time to rest.
もう帰るの？
相変わらずせわしないわね
ああ もうちょっと長居するつもり
だったんだけどな
Yeah, I was planning to stay a little longer at first.
Huh?
え？
I'll be coming back as soon as I turn in my resignation.
会社に辞表出したら
すぐこっちに帰ってくる
辞表？
Resignation?! So something did happen to you...
じゃあんた やっぱり何か…
Oh, no. It's nothing.
いや あいや 別に何も…
ん？
Well, I suppose something did happen.
ないってこともなかったんだけどさ
I decided that right now, I want to be with Kaede.
今は楓のそばにいてやりたいと思って
それに 約束したんだよ
Besides, I made a promise.
Right, Kaede?
な？　楓
Uh-huh.
うん
A promise? Kotetsu...
約束って 虎徹…
I'm vintage, Mom.
俺はヴィンテージなんだよ
母ちゃん
はあ？
Huh?
It's time to move on with my life.
シュテルンビルトは卒業ってことだ
Well, I'm off.
そいじゃ 俺行くわ
Dad, are you really going to come back soon?
お父さん　ホントにすぐに帰ってくる？
Yeah. I'll come home right after I quit my job.
ああ！　仕事辞めたら
必ずすぐ戻ってくる
You swear? It's a promise!
ホントだよ！　約束だからね？
I know, Kaede.
わかってるって 楓
あっ
ほら 危ねえぞ？
Hey, look out.
Kaede!
楓！
おい…
Huh? You're...
いっ お前…
Come back soon, okay?! Here!
早く帰ってきてね！
これ 約束の印！
This is for you to remember our promise!
R-Right...
うお？　おお
え？　あいつ…
She's... becoming a NEXT?
もしかしてＮＥＸＴに…
Kaede?
楓！
Huh?
きゃっ ああっ ぐう
ふはははは
She really is my girl.
やっぱりあいつは俺の子だな
ああっ
なあ友恵　俺は楓のヒーローで
い続ければいいんだろ？
You know, Tomoe... I can still go on as Kaede's Hero.
I'm not going back on our promise, right?
お前との約束
破ってねえよな？
灰色に染まる街の片隅で
hai iro ni somaru machi no katasumi de souzou dake no yume wo miteita
In an obscure corner of the ashen city, I was having a surreal dream.
想像だけの夢をみていた
存在する事の意味を
sonzai suru koto no imi wo nantonaku kangaehajimeta
I started to think about the meaning of existence.
なんとなく考え始めた
But I never know
BUT, I NEVER KNOW.
But, I never know.
myself＆夢＆
MYSELF AND yume AND TRUE AND ANYMORE
Myself & dreams & truth & anymore.
true＆Anymore
もう… もっと…
mou... motto...
At all...
こんな世界で私に聞いたの
konna sekai de watashi ni kita no ittai nani ga dekiru no ka wo
I asked myself what one can do in a world like this.
一体何が出来るのかを
あなたの笑顔が教えてくれたような
anata no egao ga oshiete kureta youna sonna kigashita kara
And I felt that your smiling face could teach me the answer.
そんな気がしたから
光を見つけたような
hikari wo mitsuketa youna itami ni furerareru
And enabled me to be touched by the pain of finding light.
痛みに触れられる
そう そんな気がした
sou, sonna kigashita
Yes, that was the feeling.
人は皆儚い夢を
hito wa mina hakanai yume wo kono te ni ireru tame ni
In pursuing their fleeting dreams,
この手に入れる為に
永遠の真実さえ
eien no shinjitsu sae miushinau
people lose sight of the eternal truth.
見失う
消えない悲しい明日に
kienai kanashii asu ni hikari wo kureta no wa daredemo naku tatta hitori
No one made me realize that there is a light that never dims but you,
光をくれたのは
誰でもなく たった一人
過去も未来も
shinjitai
I want to believe.
kako mo mirai mo wakachiaeru zutto
always sharing the past and the future.
分かち合えるずっと
はーい！
TIGER ＆ BUNNYの
体は首から洗うほう
Hi! I'm Barnaby, the member of Tiger & Bunny
バーナビーです
えっ あの女が 目を覚ました？
who always washes his neck first!
What? She's awakened?
これでついにウロボロスの真相が…
Now we can find out the truth about Ouroboros!
次回　TIGER ＆ BUNNY
Ignorance is bliss
Next time on Tiger & Bunny:
See you
See you!